sawaal.com 2013-01-20

# Privacy Policy - Interview Questions and Answers

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: email address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

\- To send answer notification emails (If selected to receive) 

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future notification emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. 

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you access your personal information. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information 

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on December 12th, 2012.
